Guide to the Sallie Bingham Papers, 1900-2023 and undated RL.00112
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Addition (2011-0064), 2009-2011 and undated, 1 box
  - Writings (Box Acc. 11/064: Box 1)
    - Stories for Sarah
      - Exchange (Box Acc. 11/064: Box 1)
      - Seagull (Box Acc. 11/064: Box 1)
      - Heaven (Box Acc. 11/064: Box 1)
      - Mending (Box Acc. 11/064: Box 1)
      - Selling the Farm (Box Acc. 11/064: Box 1)
    - Unselfishness (Box Acc. 11/064: Box 1)
    - Venus, Goddess of Love and Money (Box Acc. 11/064: Box 1)
    - A Villa in Tuscany (Box Acc. 11/064: Box 1)
    - Writing Women (Box Acc. 11/064: Box 1)
  - Ariadne Work (Box Acc. 11/064: Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 2009-2011 and undated (Box Acc. 11/064: Box 1)
  - Draft notes (Box Acc. 11/064: Box 1)
  - Horse Cave Anthology (Box Acc. 11/064: Box 1)
  - Las Cruces (Box Acc. 11/064: Box 1)
  - New York Society Library event, 2010 Nov. (Box Acc. 11/064: Box 1)
  - Photographs (Box Acc. 11/064: Box 1)
  - Press coverage, 2008-2010 (Box Acc. 11/064: Box 1)
  - Website (Box Acc. 11/064: Box 1)
  - Western Kentucky (Box Acc. 11/064: Box 1)
  - Women Moving Millions Impact Study interview, 2010 (Box Acc. 11/064: Box 1)
- Accessions (2011-0209) and (2011-1005), 1971-2011 and undated, 2 boxes
  Includes personal and professional correspondence, drafts of short stories, notebooks and a diary, Kentucky Old Mill Association and Kentucky Foundation for Women materials, press materials, journal articles, information regarding Bingham's book tours and readings, and more. Includes 35 mm slides in the New York Garden folder.
  - Correspondence, 2011 May-August (Box 1)
  - Writings
    - First drafts (Box 1)
    - Final Refill (Box 1)
    - The Laguna Master (Box 1)
    - Mending (Box 1)
    - New short stories, 2009 (Box 1)
    - New short stories, 2011 (Box 1)
  - Diaries and Notebooks
    - Large notebook (Box 1)
    - Small notebook, 2011 April (Box 1)
    - Diary, 2010 August-2011 March (Box 1)
  - Kentucky Old Mill Association's The Millstone, Spring 2005 (Box 2)
  - Christmas dinner, 2008 (Box 2)
  - Photographs and prints of paintings by Ann Cooper Dobbins (Box 2)
  - Kentucky Foundation for Women, 2010-2011 (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous, 2010 (Box 2)
  - Ariadne and Iona Ellsworth (Box 2)
  - Louisville Collegiate School, Class of 1954-2011 (Box 2)
  - Photographs, 2009 (Box 2)
  - Natal Chart, 2011 (Box 2)
  - Libraries that received Sallie's books, 2009 (Box 2)
  - Truchas Community Center (Box 2)
  - New York Garden papers and slides, 1994-2009 (Box 2)
  - Book tour for Mending, Fall 2011 (Box 2)
  - Book reading in Prospect, KY, September 24, 2011 (Box 2)
  - Press, 2011 (Box 2)
  - Ms. article, 1986 June (Box 2)
  - Courier Journal articles, 1970s-1980s (Box 2)
- Accession (2013-0070), 1993-2011
  - The Blue Box drafts (Box 1)
  - Trost Scholarship, Collegiate School, 2012 (Box 1)
  - Collegiate material, 2011 (Box 1)
  - Duke University endowment fund records, 2011-2013 (Box 1)
  - Iona Ellsworth (Box 1)
  - Ezra, 2012 (Box 1)
  - Euclid - St. Johns Graduate, 2012 (Box 1)
  - Filson Club, May 2012 (Box 1)
  - First drafts short stories, 2011-2013 (Box 1)
  - For my projects (Box 1)
  - Hopscotch: mission (Box 1)
  - Hopscotch House - history (Box 1)
  - Kentucky Foundation for Women (KFW) (Box 1)
  - KFW - Application (Box 1)
  - Letters, 2011-2013 (Box 1)
  - Letters, fundraising, and thank yous, 2011-2013 (Box 2)
  - Lexington, KY Literary Feasts, 2012 (Box 2)
  - Louisville Collegiate School clipping, 2012 (Box 2)
  - Misc. - reviews, news stories, etc. (Box 2)
  - News stories Re the sale (Box 2)
  - Plays, 2012 (Box 2)
  - Collegiate Classmates (Box 2)
  - Royalty statements (Box 2)
  - Sarabande Books, 2012 (Box 2)
  - Short stories - first and final drafts, 2011-2013 (Box 2)
  - Truchas Summer Program, 2011 (Box 2)
  - Wolf Pen Farm, KY (Box 2)
  - Women Writing Women's Lives, March 2012 (Box 2)
  - Women's International Study Center, Santa Fe, NM, 2011 (Box 2)
  - Diary and notebook, 1993-1994 (Box 3)
  - Poetry notebooks, 2005-2006 (Box 3)
  - Diaries, 2008-2010 (Box 3)
  - Diaries and notebooks, 2011 (Box 3)
  - Short story journal, 2011 (Box 3)
  - Diaries and notebooks, undated (Box 3)
- Accessions (2014-0134) and (2014-0135), circa 2012-2014
  Scope and Contents
  Addition comprises items related to published works along with Bingham's working files. There is a proof copy of THE BLUE BOX, an annotated typescript of "My Place," a book proposal for "Inheritance: Millicent Rogers, the Standard Oil Fortune, and the Mixed Blessing of Family Wealth," a handwritten draft of "The Last Romance," along with drafts of short stories (2013). Also includes notes on a play "Mary Breckenridge," speeches, color and black-and-white photographs (mainly documenting her family and dance), "This I believe" essay, "Women Moving Millions" file, letters, announcements, cards etc. (2012-2014), sales/royalties information for "Red Car," and printed material (Showbill for "Paducah", Modern Millwright v. 1, 2014 Sarabande Books catalog, and bound bibliography of Mary Caperton Bingham and George Barry Bingham Library).
  - Writings, family photographs, speeches, cards, and other files, circa 2012-2014 (Box Acc. 14/0134: Box 1)
- Accession (2015-0058), circa 2014-2015
  - Writings, family photographs, speeches, ephemera, and other files, circa 2014-2015 (Box Acc. 15/0058: Box 1)
  - Research files and family papers, circa 2014-2015 (Box Acc. 15/0058: Box 2)
  - Research files and other material, circa 2014-2015 (Box Acc. 15/0058: Box 3)
- Accession (2016-0015), 2013-2016
  - Research files, personal correspondence, and other material, 2013-2016 (Box Acc. 16/0015: Box 1)
    Doris Duke research (8 folders) 2013, Bingham Legacy Family snapshots (contemporary photos), Shadows, a play in four acts by H.W.B. and G.B.B., Emily's oral history, Radcliffe letters, 2011, letter 1990, Heiress book proposal (undated). KFW 2010 2 folders, Canada July 2015, Milk of Paradise play by Sallie Bingham, 1980, Women's Writing, Women's Lives conference 2015, Blue Book contract, 2011, Sarabande agreement 2009, Collegiate School photos, 1954 (photocopies), Bonnie's Class 2015, Telling Stories final draft 2010, mss draft dated 2015, The Proposal: Little Brother (undated), personal correspondence 2015 (2 folders), Mary Bingham Greece, 1928-1929, Emily's birth certificate, Correspondence with Emily 2015, Clippings 2015, 9 Journals and notebooks 2013-2015
- Accession (2016-0301), 1958-2016
  - Letters and cards, 2015-2016 (Box Acc. 16/0301: Box 1)
  - Election ephemera, 2016 (Box Acc. 16/0301: Box 1)
  - Charitable giving and financial files, 2016 (Box Acc. 16/0301: Box 1)
  - Ezra's photo and short stories, 2016 (Box Acc. 16/0301: Box 1)
  - Henry stories, 2016 (Box Acc. 16/0301: Box 1)
  - Morehead Talk, 2016 (Box Acc. 16/0301: Box 1)
  - New Mexico Conservation Voters, 2016 (Box Acc. 16/0301: Box 1)
  - For Green Fire Times article, 2016 (Box Acc. 16/0301: Box 1)
  - "Sallie Studies" article, 1958 (Box Acc. 16/0301: Box 1)
  - Wolf Pen Branch Farm field trip, 2016 (Box Acc. 16/0301: Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous programs and clippings, 1972; 2016 (Box Acc. 16/0301: Box 1)
  - Writings, 2005; 2015-2016 (Box Acc. 16/0301: Box 1)
  - Editorial notes for Doris Duke manuscript, circa 2015 (Box Acc. 16/0301: Box 1)
  - Doris Duke manuscript draft, 2015 December 28; 2 folders (Box Acc. 16/0301: Box 1)
  - Calyx 21, no. 1, Winter 2003 (Box Acc. 16/0301: Box 1)
    Contains a short story written by Sallie Bingham, "The Splinter."
  - Fiduciary Trust International, 2015-2016 (Box Acc. 16/0301: Box 1)
  - Journals and notebooks, 2004; 2011-2016 (Box Acc. 16/0301: Box 2)
- Accession (2017-0125), circa 1943; 2002-2017; 5 Volumes
  - Photographs, circa 1943 (Box Acc. 17/0125: Box 1)
  - Horse Nation, 2014-2015 (Box Acc. 17/0125: Box 1)
  - Letters and cards, 2016-2017; 3 folders (Box Acc. 17/0125: Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous clippings and programs, 2017 (Box Acc. 17/0125: Box 1)
  - Charitable giving and financial files, 2016-2017 (Box Acc. 17/0125: Box 1)
  - Writings, 2016-2017 (Box Acc. 17/0125: Box 1)
  - Doris Duke manuscript draft, 2017 February 13; 5 folders (Box Acc. 17/0125: Box 1)
  - Sallie's Reviews [book], 2002-2014 (Box Acc. 17/0125: Box 1)
  - Journals and notebooks, 2016-2017; 10 Volumes (Box Acc. 17/0125: Box 2)
- Accession (2018-0167), 1974; 2016-2018
  - Oh Beautiful City of Dreams [photocopies], circa 2017-2018 (Box Acc. 18/0167: Box 1)
  - Couvade, 2016 (Box Acc. 18/0167: Box 1)
  - The Eyes of Addicts, circa 2017-2018 (Box Acc. 18/0167: Box 1)
  - New York - Durham, 2018 April - May (Box Acc. 18/0167: Box 1)
  - Letters and cards, 2017-2018; 2 folders (Box Acc. 18/0167: Box 1)
  - Charitable giving and financial files, 2017-2018 (Box Acc. 18/0167: Box 1)
  - Playgirl magazine, 1974 May (Box Acc. 18/0167: Box 1)
  - Christmas Eve Party Santa Fe, 2017 December 31 (Box Acc. 18/0167: Box 1)
  - Blog July 7, 2017 (Box Acc. 18/0167: Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous articles and programs, 2017-2018 (Box Acc. 18/0167: Box 1)
  - Writings, 2017-2018 (Box Acc. 18/0167: Box 1)
  - Journals and notebooks, 2017-2018; 5 Volumes (Box Acc. 18/0167: Box 2)
  - Doris Duke manuscript draft, 2017 June 22 (Box Acc. 18/0167: Box 2)
- Accession (2020-0089), circa 2019-2020
  - Personal and professional files, circa 2019-2020 (Box Acc. 20/0089: Box 1)
    Includes short stories, letters and cards, notes, and other files.
- Accession (2021-0030), 1929-2021
  - Writings, letters and cards, journals, family papers, and other files, 1929-2021 (Box Acc. 21/0030: Box 1)
- Accession (2021-0083), 1942-2021
  - Edits: Little Brother, circa 2015-2021 (Box Acc. 21/0083: Box 1)
  - Note to Jonathan after his baptism, 1942 (Box Acc. 21/0083: Box 1)
  - Barry Bingham World War II, circa 1942-1945 (Box Acc. 21/0083: Box 1)
  - Brooks School, 1956 (Box Acc. 21/0083: Box 1)
  - Party for Jonathan, 1959 (Box Acc. 21/0083: Box 1)
  - Johnathan's diary and lock of hair, 1963 (Box Acc. 21/0083: Box 1)
  - Matierials related to Jonathan, 1949-1965 (Box Acc. 21/0083: Box 1)
  - Notes for Jonathan book, circa 2015-2021 (Box Acc. 21/0083: Box 1)
  - Jonathan's play, circa 1942-1964 (Box Acc. 21/0083: Box 1)
  - Enid Yandell research, circa 1942-2021 (Box Acc. 21/0083: Box 1)
  - Letters from college friends to Sallie Bingham, 1955 (Box Acc. 21/0083: Box 1)
  - Trouble on Wretched Horse Ranch [play], circa 1942-2021 (Box Acc. 21/0083: Box 1)
  - Notebook: Santa Fe Book Group--My Roles, circa 1942-2021 (Box Acc. 21/0083: Box 1)
  - Wolf Pen Mill-History, Restoration, Terms, circa 1942-2021 (Box Acc. 21/0083: Box 1)
  - Sallie Bingham Archive for Women's History, Duke, 2021 June (Box Acc. 21/0083: Box 1)
    Material related to a panel presentation by Sallie Bingham.
  - Unpublished short stories, circa 1942-2021 (Box Acc. 21/0083: Box 1)
  - Research for the Blue Box, circa 1942-2021 (Box Acc. 21/0083: Box 1)
  - Research for the Silver Swan, circa 1942-2021 (Box Acc. 21/0083: Box 1)
  - Personal cards and letters, circa 1942-2021 (Box Acc. 21/0083: Box 1)
  - Letters to the editor, circa 1942-2021 (Box Acc. 21/0083: Box 1)
  - First draft of Captive, circa 1942-2021 (Box Acc. 21/0083: Box 1)
- Accession (2022-0042), 1946-2022
  - Bingham Military School catalog, 1919-1920 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - The Filson 21, no. 3, 2021 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Enid Yandell folder, 2019-2021 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Radcliffe College Alumnae Oral History Project, 2020 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
    Includes interviews with Sallie Bingham.
  - PR for Swan [The Silver Swan], 2021 August (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Jonathan Paris, 1949 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
    Class photograph including Johnathan Bingham.
  - Jonathan Obituary, 1964 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Friendship Bridge annual report, 2020 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Letters and cards, 2021-2022 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Mother's family (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Mary Lily Kenan Flagler Fund, 2013 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - My contributions to Duke, 2015-2021 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Truchas Community Center, 2016 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - The Artist as Activist, 2021 June (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Kentucky Foundation for Women Day, 2021 October (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Notes on jury duty, 2021 November (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Proposal for a biography of Lady Mary Wortley Montague, circa 2021 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Author's questionnaire, 2015 January (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - 1950s clippings, letters, and other material about Sallie (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Book reviews, circa 1980s (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - The Ranch, 2021 May (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Hilda edited chapters, circa 2021 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Letters to the editor, 2021 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - For Duke, 2015-2020 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
    Includes a notebook with material for an autobiography, as well as writings and poetry by Sallie.
  - The American Voice no. 45, 1998 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Planner, 2017 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Hiking notebook, 2017-2018; 2021 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Notebook, 2021 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Jonathan USB, 2021 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
    Contains images of Sallie and Johnathan Bingham.
  - Sallie's Page A Day Diary, 1946 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
- Accession (2022-0073), 1939-2022
  Materials in this accession are research files for Sallie's book "Little Brother" about her younger brother Johnathan Worth Bingham.
  - Harvard Psychedelic Club [Empty folder], 1950s-1960s (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Cordie, Lizzie, Ollie, Curt, 2009 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
    Includes genealogical research and oral history interviews related to Bingham family servants.
  - Birth, 1942 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Henry Wallace / FDR 1944, circa 2015-2020 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
    Excerpts from an undated oral history interview.
  - Office of Civilian Defense, Washington, 1941 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Mary to ER [Eleanor Roosevelt], 1944 July (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Little Brother proposal and outline, circa 2015-2016 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Jonathan's party list, 1948 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Confirmation: June 3, 1956, 13 years old, 1956 June 13 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Little Brother first draft proposal, 2015-2016 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Ballard School, 1948-1951 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Little Brother sample chapter, circa 2015-2016 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Little Brother proposal, 2016 February (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Birth: Background notes, Washington, and war, 1940-1942 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Little Brother: The servants, circa 2015-2020 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Santa Fe Writers Group: First meeting, 2020 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Inserted: Little Brother, Father's letter 1941, circa 2015-2020 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Little Brother for editing, 2020 February 25 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Taos Feb. 25, 2020, 2020 February 25 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Taos Reading p. 11-18, 2020 February 18 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Taos Feb. 18 corrections entered, 2020 February 18 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Taos Reading 2/11/2020, 2020 February 11 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Dropping out of Harvard, 1963 September 10; circa 2015-2020 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Chapter 12 draft, 2016 September 16 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Jonathan contacts, 2021 January 25 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Gray Henry's letter, 2021 January 14 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Jonathan's friends, 2020 November 11 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Letters to Embry Feb. 1964, 1964 February; 2021 January 08 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Brooks obituary, circa 1964 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Brooks Shield, 1958-1960 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
    Contains several issues of "The Brooks Shield" from Brooks School in North Andover, Massachusetts.
  - Jonathan's plays, circa 1940s-1950s (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Labels for Geniac, circa 1950s (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Mother's letters: Paying off mortgage, "The General", circa 1950s (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Letters, Coroner's report, Death, 1964 March 07; 1968; 1989 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Mother's letter to Mr. Ashburn re: Jonathan, 1956 March 14 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Sound and the Fury notes, circa 2015-2020 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Death: March 7, 1964, 2010 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Jonathan's letters to parents freshman year, 1960-1961 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Father's political letters 1940-1941, 1939-1944 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Father's letter to me re: Johnathan, 1963 July 30 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Lineman's clothing, 2020 November 04 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Coroner's report, funeral, estate, circa 2015-2020 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - My journal 6/1960 [photocopies], 1960 June (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Jonathan Rumpelstiltskin Life photo, circa 1950s (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - My letters to Jonathan, circa 1960s (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Jonathan Daniels, 1942 June 03 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Proposal: Little Brother 10/2017, 2017 October 09 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Jonathan and Vietnam, 2017 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Jonathan and Civil Rights, 2017 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Information from my archive at Duke, circa 2015-2020 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Corky Short letter, 1987; 2016 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Brooks School grades, 1956-1960 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Jonathan Kennedey assassination 1963, circa 2015-2020 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Harvard 1962/63, 1961-1963 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - LBJ Kentucky 1964, 2015 April (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
    Contains an article from 2015 about Lyndon B. Johnson's 1964 visit to Kentucky.
  - Brooks School: Letter, Lusk report, 1959 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Brooks School rules, 1950s (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Work at the Courier 1959, 1959 June 26 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Debut Party, 1959 September (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Independent School Tour, 1962 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Unnatural Acts Harvard 1920, 2011; 2016 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Country Day, 1953-1956 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Brooks School, 1958-1959 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Mary's report for National Merit Scholarship, circa 1950s (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Boy Scouts, circa 2015-2020 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Photo with me [photocopy], 1958; circa 2015-2020 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Lionel train set giveaway 1959, 1959 December 31 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Sleeping problems articles, circa 1961 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Antonia Fraser: Files kept on child, circa 2015 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Mary re: Jonathan, 1954 May 04 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Acceptance letters Brooks 1956, 1956 April 11 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Manda's letter, 1960 July 13 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Mary's letter, 1942 September 09 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Camp St. John's military school, 1953 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Mary's speech, 1959; 2006 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Jonathan - Filson, 1942-1951 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Lady Undina of Gump, circa 1940s-1950s (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
    A play by Johnathan Bingham.
  - Clans Symbols and nameplate, circa 1950s-1960s (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Little Brother, 2015 November (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
  - Cassette tape and floppy disk with interviews, 2009 (Box Acc. 22/0042: Box 1)
- Accession (2023-0072), 2003-2023
  - History, 2003; circa 2000s (Box Acc. 23/072: Box 1)
    Contains photocopies of material related to Bingham family history, as well as Laura Carpenter Bingham's master's thesis entitled "Philanthropy at Women's College: Peace College in the 1920s and the 1960s."
  - Copyright registration, 2022 (Box Acc. 23/072: Box 1)
    For Bingham's book Little Brother.
  - Events, 2022-2023 (Box Acc. 23/072: Box 1)
  - Writings, 2020-2022 (Box Acc. 23/072: Box 1)
    Includes draft essays, published op-ed pieces, personal writings, and correspondence related to writing projects.
  - Edits: Will's Things (Two Silver Cups), 2022 June 21 (Box Acc. 23/072: Box 1)
  - Edits: Will's Things (Two Silver Cups), 2022 September 09 (Box Acc. 23/072: Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 2022-2023; 2 folders (Box Acc. 23/072: Box 1)
    Also includes photocopied materials from the 1980s and 1990s related to the Bingham family.
  - Journals, 2020 (Box Acc. 23/072: Box 1)
  - Journals, 2013, 2022 (Box Acc. 23/072: Box 2)